# Joe Parsley

joewparsley.com
(503)-305-1030 joewparsley@gmail.com
GitHub LinkedIn

## **Profile Summary:**

Upbeat and Versatile Front-end Web Developer with a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail and good attitude to go with it. I've worked with numerous small teams where many hats are worn and crunch time is always around the corner. Where I fit on a team is wherever I'm needed most!

## **Core Competencies:**

AngularJS | JavaScript | ReactJS | TypeScript |
Ionic | Mobile Development | CSS/SASS | HTML |
UI/UX Design | Responsive Design | Angular
Material | Front-end Frameworks | Time
Management | Project Management | Sketch3 |

## **Projects:**

- Vingo (soon to be on the app store)
- Vingo.car
- Flight.run
- <u>Scatterschool.com</u>
- Bimearth.com

## **Education** April 2017 - Sep 2017

**Epicodus:** Course: Front-end/Design

At Epicodus I learned the ins and outs of front-end web development. Primarily working with Angular, Typescript and SASS/HTML. More Importantly I learned how to problem solve with others and how to properly research new libraries and frameworks!

#### **Experience**

#### Flight - UI/UX Engineer Oct 2017 - Present

- Design UI for new contracts and clients
- Work closely with small teams in an agile development environment
- Build fully responsive web apps using custom HTML/SCSS or popular front-end frameworks if needed
- Build out components and maintain file structure for projects
- Maintain front-end on company projects (flight.run and scatterschool.com)

#### **Client Contracts while at Flight:**

<u>Vingo</u> - February 2018 - May 2018

 For this client I was responsible for building the front-end of their consumer phone app based off of designs from their designer. After I finished their phone app I was able to go on and build out their consumer and dealership facing websites. I worked closely with all members of the Vingo team to make sure the product I delivered to them was exactly what they asked for.

#### BIM Earth - December 2018 - February 2018

 For this client I was asked not only to build out the front-end of this project but to design the UI from the ground up. I was able to meet with the client many times and together we were able to take an idea and turn it into something real. This project is still in the prototype state while the client searches for investment!